{
    "id": "2ed55a500413491c8168f2db1f36089a",
    "title": "Time expressions used with tenses",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3dec8f7d81ab42d78912e78d42a0e999",
            "title": "Time Expressions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ..................................... breakfast at 8 am every day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ....................................... breakfast at 8 am yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "has",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog ........................................ all night yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is barking",
                        "was barking",
                        "has been barking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog .................................... at the moment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "barks",
                        "is barking",
                        "barked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The dog ................................... for hours last night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was barking",
                        "has barked",
                        "barked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .......................................... the newspaper every morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "read",
                        "have read",
                        "was reading"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ....................................... the newspaper at the moment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "read",
                        "am reading",
                        "was reading"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ................................... me English for three hours last Sunday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "taught",
                        "is teaching",
                        "has taught"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ................................... me English at the moment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "teaches",
                        "is teaching",
                        "taught"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ..................................... me English every day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "teaches",
                        "is teaching",
                        "has taught"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}